Guide to the Stephen M. Cabrinety Collection in the History of Microcomputing, ca. 1975-1995
Department of Special Collections
- Software, Series 1
  - Games, Subseries 1.4
    - Unknown, Inc. Zap!, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - US Games Corporation Gopher, 1982, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 218)
    - US Gold Dive Bomber, 1988, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 145)
    - US Gold Metro cross, 1988, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 113)
    - US Gold Tower Toppler, 1988, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 145)
    - Us Gold Inc E-Motion, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 74)
    - US Gold Inc Sports-A-Roni, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 36)
    - US Gold, Inc. Super Putty, 1991, computer cartridgeSuper Nintendo (Box 9)
    - Us Gold Inc Tower Toppler, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 37)
    - Velocity Spectre, 1992, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 5)
    - Verbatim Memory Castle, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 219)
    - Verbatim Paws: Side 1 #1-8, Side 2 #9-16, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 219)
    - Verisoft Works Computer Easy: Schultz's Treasure, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 61)
    - Vic Tokai, Inc. Conflict, 1989, computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - Vic Tokai, Inc. Daedalian Opus, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 206)
    - Vic Tokai, Inc. Golgo 13: Top Secret Episode, n.d., 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 204)
    - Vic Tokai, Inc. King Salmon: "the big catch", 1992, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Vic Tokai, Inc. Socket, 1993, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Vic Tokai, Inc. The Krion Conquest, 1990, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 202)
    - Vic Tokai, Inc. Top Secret Episode: Golgo 13, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 204)
    - Victory Software Corporation Adventure Pack II, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore (Box 187)
    - Victory Software Corporation Night Rider, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Victory Software Corporation Strategy Pack 1, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Video Wizard Galactic Defender, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 211)
    - Viking Technologies, Inc. The best of Up Time, brought to you by Mac World, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 106)
    - Viking Technologies, Inc. Up Time.--Vol. 1, no. 12, 1987, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 106)
    - Villa Crespo Software, Inc. Coffee Break CD Collection: 21 Games for Everybody, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.MS-DOS (Box 12)
    - Virgin Rick Davis's World Trophy Soccer, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 129)
    - Virgin Enterprises, Ltd. Chuck Rock II: Son of Chuck, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Virgin Enterprises, Ltd. Jammit, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Virgin Enterprises, Ltd. Robocop versus The Terminator, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSega Genesis (Box 208)
    - Virgin Games Double Dragon II: The revenge, 1989, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 172)
    - Virgin Games Double Dragon II: The revenge, 1989, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 184)
    - Virgin Games Falcon Patrol Demo, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Unknown (Box 219)
    - Virgin Games Heimdall the Viking, 1992, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 158)
    - Virgin Games Sorcery Plus, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 143)
    - Virgin Games Vengeance Of Excalibur, 1991, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in.; 3 ½ in.DOS (Box 160)
    - Virgin Games, Inc. Cool Spot, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 6)
    - Virgin Games Inc Dune, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.MS-DOS (Box 12)
    - Virgin Games, Inc. Floor 13, 1992, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 168)
    - Virgin Games, Inc. Muhammad Ali: Heavyweight Boxing, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 206)
    - Virgin Games, Inc. Overlord, 1992, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - Virgin Games, Inc. Prince of Persia by Jordan Mechner, 1992, 1 computer cartridgeNintendo (Box 10)
    - Virgin Games, Inc. Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves, 1989, 1 computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 206)
    - Virgin Games, Inc. The Computer Edition of Monopoly: Parker Brothers Real Estate Trading Game, 1991, computer disk; 3 ½ in. MS-DOS (Box 17)
    - Virgin Games, Ltd. Sorcery Plus, 1988, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 101)
    - Virgin Interactive Entertainment, Inc. Robocop versus The Terminator, 1993, 1 computer cartridgeSEGA Game Gear (Box 207)
    - Virgin Malbourne House Demon's Tomb The Awakening, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 100)
    - Virgin Mastertronic Int'l, Inc. Hunter Patrol, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 31)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. 7-up proudly presents Spot: The Computer Game, 1990, 1 computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 159)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Back To Reality, 1986, 1 computer cassetteCommodore (Box 187)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. BMX Racer, n.d, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 184)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. BMX Racers, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 200)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. BMX Trials / 1985: The Day After, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 182)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Bounder, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 194)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. California Pro Golf, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 165)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Candidate, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 103)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Candidate, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 193)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Captain Zapp, n.d, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 183)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Chiller, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 200)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Chopper X, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 154)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Clue Master Detective, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 61)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Demon's Tomb: the awakening, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 160)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Elektraglide, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Excaliba / Big Mac, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Feud: Battle of the Wizards, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 185)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Grimblood, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 151)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. House of Cards, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 161)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Ice Palace / Hop to, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 188)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Ivan 'Ironman' Stewart's Super Off Road, 1990, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 103)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. James Clavell's Shogun, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore; IBM PC (Box 35)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. James Clavell's Shogun, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS; IBM PC (Box 169)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Kane / The Human Race, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 177)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Kikstart 2 plus course designer, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Kikstart 2: Plus course designer, n.d, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 183)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Kikstart Off-Road Simulator, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 203)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Knight Games, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Knight Games, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 194)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Kobyashi Naru, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 157)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Las Vegas Video Poker, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 194)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Master Chess, 1986, 1 computer cassetteCommodore (Box 187)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Metropolis, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 157)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Molecule Man, 1986, 1 computer cassetteCommodore (Box 187)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Monty Python's Flying Circus, 1991, computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 19)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Ninja, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 161)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Ninja, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Ninja, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Ninja Mission, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Amiga (Box 42)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. One Man & His Droid / Nonterraqueous, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 182)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Panther, 1986, 1 computer cassetteCommodore (Box 187)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Phantom of the Asteroid / Hek Tik, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 188)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Pro Golf, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 157)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Pro Golf, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 172)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Pro Golf, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 194)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Prowler, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 34)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Renegade, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 76)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Scrabble Brand Crossword Game, 1989, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 129)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Skyjet, n.d, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 184)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Speed King, 1986, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Spirit of Excalibur, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 162)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Storm, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 165)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Street Fighting Man, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 69)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. The Last V8, 1985, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 178)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. The Last V8, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore 64/128 (Box 203)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. The quest for the Holy Grail, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 179)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Tri-Action Games, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 157)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Turbo Champions, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 165)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Wing Commander Sky Jet, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 38)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. Xenon, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 71)
    - Virgin Mastertronic International, Inc. ZUB: You won't zub me this time, you .... ZUBS! (initiate written shooting sounds)., 1986, 1 computer cassetteCommodore (Box 187)
    - Virgin Melbourne House Rick Davis's World Trophy Soccer, n.d., computer disk; 3 ½ in. Amiga (Box 102)
    - Vision Software Addition/ Subtraction, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Vision Software Multiplication/ Division, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 197)
    - Vital Information, Inc. The Flockland Island Crisis, 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; Atari (Box 123)
    - Vivid Image Developments, Ltd. Time Machine, 1990, 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Atari (Box 131)
    - Voyager Software Gator Beach, 1981, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 212)
    - VSS, Inc. Finders Keepers program disk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 152)
    - Wadsworth Electronic Publishing Company Algebra Arcade, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 59)
    - Walt Disney Computer Software, Inc. Dick Tracy: Crimestoppers Print Kit, 1992, computer disk; 3 ½ in. DOS (Box 170)
    - Wayne Green, Inc. Carnival Companion, 1982, 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 145)
    - Weekly Reader Family Software Beach Landing by Richard Hefter and Susan Dubicki, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 109)
    - Weekly Reader Family Software Beach Landing by Richard Hefter and Susan Dubicki, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 117)
    - Weekly Reader Family Software Beach Landing by Richard Hefter and Susan Dubicki, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 132)
    - Weekly Reader Family Software Codes and Cyphers, 1984, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 106)
    - Weekly Reader Family Software Old Ironsides by Jack Rice and Richard Hefter [2 copies], 1982, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 109)
    - Weekly Reader Family Software Run For It, 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 132)
    - Westone Co., Ltd. Wonderboy in Monster World, 1989, computer cartridgeGenesis (Sega) (Box 7)
    - Wheeling, IL: Taito America Corp. Elevator Action, 1991, computer cartridgeGame Boy (Nintendo) (Box 8)
    - Williams Electronics, Inc. Defender, 1981, 1 computer cartridgeAtari (Box 219)
    - Windcrest Software, Inc. Baseball's Best by George A. Schwenk, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 127)
    - Wizardware Multimedia, Ltd. CD-ROM Mega Mix, n.d., computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 174)
    - Wizardware Multimedia, Ltd. Gif Galaxy CDROM: Volume 1 (shareware), 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 174)
    - Wizardware Multimedia, Ltd. House of Games (shareware), 1992, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 174)
    - WizardWorks Challenge Pack for Windows: includes 7 games, n.d., 2 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Windows (Box 2)
    - Wunderware It's a Living, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 39)
    - Wunderware Mad Painter!, 1982, 1 computer cassetteCommodore VIC-20 (Box 39)
    - Xetec, Inc. Font Master 128, 1988, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 190)
    - Xlent Software The Trivia Construction Set: Trivia Mania, 1985, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 156)
    - XONOX, Inc. Artillery Duel, 1983, 1 computer cartridgeColecoVision & ADAM (Box 213)
    - XOR Corp. Basketball Challenge, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 166)
    - XOR Corp. NFL Challenge, n.d., 1 computer disk; 3 ½ in. Macintosh (Box 52)
    - Xor Corp NFL Challenge, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 66)
    - XOR Corp. Oligopoly, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 166)
    - ZiMag Cat-Nap, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 82)
  - Miscellaneous software, Subseries 1.5
    - 3M High Density Disk-- 1.6 MB- David Wagner (14 copies), 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 219)
    - Abacus Software, Inc. Disk for the book Atari ST GEM Programmer's reference, vol. 3, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 152)
    - ACS Computer Ltd. Compro Multimedia Introductory Module, 1993, computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.DOS (Box 20)
    - Adventure International Earthquake: San Francisco 1906, 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 45)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. 130XE Artshow, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. 130XE Hi-Res Designer, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. A.I. - The Antic Index (PD), 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. A.I. - The Antic Index (PD), 1984, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. A.I. - The Antic Index (PD), 1983, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Action Utilities #1, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Action Utilities #2: Machine-Language Oriented, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Antic Forth (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Antic Monthly Disk, 1985, April, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. ArtDOS (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Astronomy & Metrorology (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Atari Mini-Film Festival (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Atari Speaks Human(PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Business and Finance (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. C.U.E.S. Edpack #1 (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. C.U.E.S. Edpack #2 (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Computer Tutor (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Crockford's Whimsy (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Database Managers & Disk Utilities (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Datagraph Data Manager, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. DOS 4.0, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Essential Utilities (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Heavy Metal Art (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Homepak Customizer (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Icon Graphics Editor, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. II Computing for Apple II users, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 72)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Micropaint Artist (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Monitor/ Debugger and more (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Personal Finance and Education, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Photo Graphics, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Programmer's Design Tools (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Radio & Electronics (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Steve Dong's Gallery (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Super Utilities #2 (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Super Utilities #3 (PD), n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Trivia Quiz, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 2, No. 10 Printers, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 2, No. 11 Personal Finance, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 2, No. 12 Worldwide Users, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 2, No. 4 Adventure Games, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 2, No. 5 Graphics, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 2, No. 6 Education, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 2, No. 7 Sports Games, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 2, No. 8 Sound and Music, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 2, No. 9 New Product Guide, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 1 Games, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 10 Finance Issue, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 11 Ultimate Printers, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 2 New XL's, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 3 Communications, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 4 Disk Drives, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 5 Graphics, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 6 Education, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 7 Adventure, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 8 Buyer's Guide, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 3, No. 9 Super Utilities, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 4, No. 1 Anniversary Issue, 1985, May, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Antic Publishing, Inc. Vol. 4, No. 2 Computer Arts, 1985, May, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Atari, Inc. Asteroids long-playing children's cassette, 1982, 1 audio cassette (Box 138)
    - Atari, Inc. Atari Speed Reading, 1981, 5 computer cassetteAtari (Box 81)
    - Atari, Inc. Domination, n.d., 1 computer cassetteAtari (Box 80)
    - Atari, Inc. Everybody is Talking Atari, 1981, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 84)
    - Atari, Inc. MARS Merchandising (44 (yes, 44...) copies, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Atari, Inc. Personal Fitness Program, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 80)
    - Atari, Inc. Public Domain Programs Graphics "Top Picks", n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 92)
    - Atari, Inc. Super Breakout read-along book and cassette, 1982, 1 audio cassette (Box 138)
    - Atari, Inc. Yars' Revenge read-along book and cassette, 1982, 1 audio cassette (Box 138)
    - Avant-Garde Publishing Corp Action sounds and hi-res scrolling, n.d., computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple; Atari (Box 123)
    - Batteries Included Photographs, Slides, & Home Movies, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 54)
    - Capcom USA, Inc. Hat Trick Disk Pak, 1987, computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 167)
    - CD ROM Galleries, Inc. Scenic & Architecture, n.d., computer laser optical disc; 4 ¾ in.Windows (Box 20)
    - CodeWriter Corporation Recipe File System, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Atari (Box 89)
    - Commodore Business Machines, Ltd. Sales Edge, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 21)
    - Concept Development Associates Inc America Cooks American, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 26)
    - Concept Development Associates Inc America Cooks Italian, 1986, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Commodore (Box 26)
    - Concept Development Associates, Inc. Award Winning Wines by Howard Kraft, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 43)
    - Concept Development Associates, Inc. Great Chefs Vol. 1-3, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 46)
    - Concept Development Associates, Inc. Great Vintage Years: Book-on-disk, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. Apple (Box 46)
    - Concept Development Associates Inc Micro Kitchen Companion, n.d., 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 66)
    - Concept Development Associates Inc Micro Kitchen Companion 3rd Edition, 1987, 1 computer disk; 5 ¼ in. DOS (Box 66)